scentiments.com 2013-05-18

# Privacy Statement

**                                      Privacy Statement  
**  
At Scentiments.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Below is a brief overview of the highlights of our Privacy Policy. This will give you a how information is collected from you and how it is used, but does not include all important information.   
 **Information Collected**  
When you shop on our site, we collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number and product selections. Credit Card numbers are not stored. We may also collect IP address, domain types (e.g. .com or .org, etc.), your browser type, the country, state and the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit.

 **How Information is Used**  
We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, enhancing the operation of our site, statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We do not use third parties to help us fulfill orders or to provide customer service. We do employ third parites to help process payments,  to serve site content, to help administer promotional emails and to administer drawings or contests. Each party we employ safeguards your privacy and will not rent or sell your information. All customers have the opportunity to opt-out at the time of purchase or during any subseuqent promotional emailing.

 **Cookies**  
We use cookies to help identify you when you visit our store and to customize your experience. The cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies.

 **Safe shopping Guarantee**  
We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at our online store. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, We will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. 

**Scentury Club Terms and Conditions  
Please [click here to learn more](http://www.scentiments.com/home/rewardsprogram.aspx)**
